Alright, in this video I will tell you how we can create a book mark, let's see an extension.
So as you can see I'm using get started with 2/0 and now I can use agents and editor.
Here just the initial tool tip, I will just start with initial agent.
Here we can open the hierarchy or maximize the chat you would like to have a more simplified
remote that you can switch between editor.
I have the previous one which looks like a fork of Visual Studio Code.
I will just use normal agent and now we use own context.
But now I want you to create a Chrome extension that will contain JavaScript book marklets.
I want you to create a list, categorize it, I want you to maybe use list and categorize
all of them and write a description for each book marklet when I hover on it.
The best way to do it because I have like a purple list of book marklets, it's in my desktop.
So I will just copy it over, go to my extension, now we're just copy it is soon appear here
on the right you see, it's a long one and then what I can do here I can just make reference
to it and first I will just ask for a plan because it will plan for me and maybe I want
to get more insights how this extension can be created.
So now I'm opening a new chat, as you can see it has been named, create a Chrome extension
for book marklet, now we can wait a little bit until it's done.
First it's thinking, so I'm planning more than need to clarify a couple critical question
for a move forward.
I like it because actually it will just ask some of it, all right.
So how should you, I will pop a window where I can categorize it, how I show the description
browser context menu and the spark category.
Yeah, I think the first one is all right so pop up window with the garage list, it's
perfect.
And get the go strategy strategy, create automatic strategy for social media platforms and
more general actually stating content or seven images, this category can be named general.
And now I will press enter, I think it will plan a new move, if not I can always switch
between plan and agent and move without a new prompt.
So creating Chrome extension plan, or I think it will just create a manifest, so we can
look, okay.
Now we prepare list, pop marklets, there is a behavior with a title on a pop up, see
a lot of it, data modeling examples, web archives, strip and there are seven to do, so the
first one is create manifest, implement pop up, so it's great because it is a JavaScript
and it will add to from book marklets to JSON, which is great because I will just remove
that, it will just pretend in book mark let JSON and there's like execute logic, so inject
navigate at such input into the description, that's great, I think.
So we just press this button and build.
So now we need to wait until it's done, I'll pause the video because it might take some
time, but we prepared.
And if you're looking for book marklets, just type book marklet online and you can see
some of the examples, and then you can ask cloud or chat JPT to write some cast to one
or just be inspired, write your own self and then populate in the text file and implement
in the cursor.
Let me see the hierarchy, you have a data, you have a manifest JSON, some permission,
tab storage, right, and there's a data inside, that's all we can remove now, let's press
delete, move to recycle bin, I'll leave it as it is and now I will go to the Chrome extension
management, how open manage, and I'll just load and pack and then from here, I will go to
bookmark it, I'll press that one, so as you can see it's now headed and now I will just
speed it up to test it, this is the search engine that I've created in the previous material
and this one is bookmark it, I don't see everything, so if I type tick tock, I don't
think I will be able to, alright so first, I don't see any, but rather search only, it doesn't
work, I don't need a search button, just populate it with folders that will have book
mark, let's tap in each category in the hover description, okay, it's pretty simplified
and I think it will be able actually to do, you have to wait and then I will be able to
make it more for that, alright I think it has been fixed, so I'm going back to my Chrome
extension here, and I will open it up, and I will open the manage extension, actually this
one, I think it's, but we have to reload first, so we go to manage, now we just restart,
there's some errors, let's speed this one after the moment, alright, this is like some
refusing something, alright, okay, so we can just copy this and from the standard point of view,
I receive this information, is there a way to bypass it as an extension, and first we can
ask. So I'll ask instead of implementing it.